<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- natural -->

  <Heart.label>心脏</Heart.label>
  <Heart.description>负责将血液和氧气供给到身体的各个位置。待候新的主人。</Heart.description>

  <Lung.label>肺</Lung.label>
  <Lung.description>呼吸系统的重要组成部分。</Lung.description>

  <Kidney.label>肾</Kidney.label>
  <Kidney.description>过滤并移除血液中的废物。</Kidney.description>

  <Liver.label>肝</Liver.label>
  <Liver.description>在新陈代谢扮演重要的角色。</Liver.description>


  <!-- simple prosthetics (industrial tech) -->

  <SimpleProstheticLeg.label>简易的假腿</SimpleProstheticLeg.label>
  <SimpleProstheticLeg.description>用来替换缺失的腿的假肢，不是很舒服但是相当有效。</SimpleProstheticLeg.description>

  <SimpleProstheticArm.label>简易的假臂</SimpleProstheticArm.label>
  <SimpleProstheticArm.description>简易但耐用的假臂。</SimpleProstheticArm.description>

  <SimpleProstheticHeart.label>prosthetic heart</SimpleProstheticHeart.label>
  <SimpleProstheticHeart.description>A heart prosthesis. It contains an electric motor that pumps blood smoothly around the body. Users often report feeling tired, but it's better than the alternative.</SimpleProstheticHeart.description>

  <CochlearImplant.label>cochlear implant</CochlearImplant.label>
  <CochlearImplant.description>text_todo</CochlearImplant.description>


  <!-- bionics (spacer tech) -->

  <BionicEye.label>仿生眼</BionicEye.label>
  <BionicEye.description>高端科技的产物，仿生眼不仅能完全替代自然眼睛的功能，还能赋予使用者超常的视力。</BionicEye.description>

  <BionicArm.label>仿生臂</BionicArm.label>
  <BionicArm.description>最精密的手臂替代品之一，赋予使用者爆发出无与伦比的力量。</BionicArm.description>

  <BionicLeg.label>仿生腿</BionicLeg.label>
  <BionicLeg.description>尖端科技制成的仿生腿，可以给使用者带来极端的步行舒适度和力量。</BionicLeg.description>

  <BionicSpine.label>bionic spine</BionicSpine.label>
  <BionicSpine.description>An advanced artificial spine. A biogel nerve bundle runs down an articulated plasteel core, surrounded by a lattice-dust healing system. It matches the performance of a biological spine.</BionicSpine.description>

  <BionicHeart.label>bionic heart</BionicHeart.label>
  <BionicHeart.description>An advanced artificial heart. It has synthetic muscle fibers for a realistic heartbeat, plus a high-flow pump for rapid circulation during high stress. It is better than a biological heart in almost every way.</BionicHeart.description>

  <BionicStomach.label>bionic stomach</BionicStomach.label>
  <BionicStomach.description>An advanced artificial stomach. A set of sensors and chemical synthesizers efficiently digest nearly any energy-bearing foodstuff. An integrated lattice-dust healing system automatically repairs any damage caused by the powerful acids. It is better than a biological stomach in almost every way.</BionicStomach.description>

  <BionicEar.label>bionic ear</BionicEar.label>
  <BionicEar.description>text_todo</BionicEar.description>


  <!-- bionic non-makeable -->

  <PowerClaw.label>动力爪</PowerClaw.label>
  <PowerClaw.description>一种由三个致命利爪组成的强大的手部替代品。</PowerClaw.description>


  <!-- archotech -->

  <ArchotechEye.label>archotech eye</ArchotechEye.label>
  <ArchotechEye.description>An artifical eye built by an archotech. It perceives every type of electromagnetic radiation, including radio waves, infrared, light, x-rays, and gamma rays. Its visual acuity is precise enough to read handwriting from twenty meters away. It can emit various wavelengths of radiation like a flashlight, and has an internal subpersona AI which helps highlight useful visual information. Externally, it looks like a natural human eye, except it can change color at will. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechEye.description>

  <ArchotechArm.label>archotech arm</ArchotechArm.label>
  <ArchotechArm.description>An artifical arm built by an archotech. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechArm.description>

  <ArchotechLeg.label>archotech leg</ArchotechLeg.label>
  <ArchotechLeg.description>An artifical leg built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but a pair of these can move the user as fast as a decent car, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLeg.description>


  <!-- artificial - simple prosthetics -->
  <!-- artificial - bionics -->
  <!--<ScytherBlade.label>飞螳镰刃</ScytherBlade.label>-->
  <!--<ScytherBlade.description>嵌有镰刃的手部替代品。从机械飞螳上拆下来的。不是很舒服但确实是非常致命的近战武器。</ScytherBlade.description>-->

</LanguageData>