<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	
	<CameraDolly.helpTexts>
		<li>按住鼠标滚轮并拖动或者使用WASD键来移动摄像机。</li>
	</CameraDolly.helpTexts>
	
	
	<Rescuing.helpTexts>
		<li>选择一名健康的殖民者并鼠标右击受伤的殖民者来进行援救。</li>
	</Rescuing.helpTexts>
	
	<Capturing.helpTexts>
		<li>有一个敌人重伤不能行动了，你可以俘虏他们！</li>
		<li>若想俘虏敌人，选择一名殖民者，右键点击重伤的敌人并选择俘虏。\n\n你必须要有至少一张给囚犯使用的空床。</li>
	</Capturing.helpTexts>
	
	<Drafting.helpTexts>
		<li>若想直接控制殖民者进行战斗，选择他们并按下“征召”按钮。</li>
		<li>被征召的殖民者只会做你命令他们做的事，并且只会做和战斗有关的动作。有武器的人会在有任何机会时自动使用武器。\n\n别忘了在不需要战斗时取消征召状态——他们不会自己去吃饭或者睡觉。</li>
	</Drafting.helpTexts>
	
	<Forbidding.helpTexts>
		<li>殖民者们不会和被标记为“已禁止”的物件互动。\n\n选中降落点附近的食物和金属并按F来取消禁止状态。</li>
	</Forbidding.helpTexts>
	
	<BillsTab.helpTexts>
      <li>若想让殖民者使用工作台，选择工作台并打开“清单”选项卡。在这里你可以选择做什么样的食物，造什么样的东西以及屠宰什么样的生物。</li>
    </BillsTab.helpTexts>
	
	<GrowingFood.helpTexts>
		<li>若想种植食物，打开建筑师并规划一些种植区。\n\n种植区只能被放置在肥沃的土地上。</li>
	</GrowingFood.helpTexts>
	
	<BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.helpTexts>
		<li>提示:\n\n若想将和轨道商人进行交易，你必须在室外建造一个轨道交易信标并且将需要交易的物品放在信标附近的贮藏区里。</li>
	</BuildOrbitalTradeBeacon.helpTexts>
	
	<ReadingAlerts.helpTexts>
		<li>如果你不知道该做些什么，检查一下屏幕右侧有没有警告。</li>
	</ReadingAlerts.helpTexts>
	
	<CameraZoom.helpTexts>
		<li>滚动鼠标滚轮或者按T键和G键来放大/缩小游戏画面。</li>
	</CameraZoom.helpTexts>
	
	<TimeControls.helpTexts>
		<li>你可以使用屏幕右下角的时间控制按钮来加快，减慢或停止时间流逝。</li>
	</TimeControls.helpTexts>
	
	<PrisonerTab.helpTexts>
		<li>ook in a prisoner's 'Prisoner' tab to set how they'll be treated.\n\nYou'll need a colonist with the Warden work to take care of the prisoner.</li>
	</PrisonerTab.helpTexts>
	
	<Mining.helpTexts>
		<li>You can designate where to mine using the ARCHITECT MENU.\n\nMining MINERALS yields METAL.\n\nMining ROCK yields nothing.</li>
	</Mining.helpTexts>
	
	<WorkOverview.helpTexts>
		<li>You can set each colonist's work settings in the OVERVIEW at the bottom right of the screen.\n\nThey will always do the highest priority work defName that they can find.</li>
		<li>Colonists won't do jobs they don't have set.\n\nIf nobody has a certain work defName assigned, it will never get done!</li>
	</WorkOverview.helpTexts>
	
	<EquippingWeapons.helpTexts>
		<li>To have your colonist equip a weapon, select the colonist and then right-click on the weapon.\n\nThere are weapons on the ground near your starting location.</li>
	</EquippingWeapons.helpTexts>
	
	<HomeRegion.helpTexts>
		<li>HOME REGIONS tell your colonists which areas to clean and where to extinguish fires.\n\nDefine a HOME REGION with the Zones category under the Architect menu.</li>
	</HomeRegion.helpTexts>
	
	<StorageTabCategories.helpTexts>
		<li>In the storage tab, you can expand categories to allow or deny specific items. Click the triangles to the left of category names.</li>
	</StorageTabCategories.helpTexts>
	
	<StorageTab.helpTexts>
		<li>You can configure stockpiles and storage buildings by selecting them and opening the STORAGE TAB above the bottom-left inspector pane.</li>
	</StorageTab.helpTexts>
	
	<SpacePause.helpTexts>
		<li>Hit SPACE to pause or unpause the game.\n\nYou can give orders while paused.\n\nRemember this - if things get hectic, just hit SPACE!</li>
	</SpacePause.helpTexts>
	
	<RightClickClearLetter.helpTexts>
		<li>You can quickly dismiss incoming letters by right-clicking them.</li>
	</RightClickClearLetter.helpTexts>
	
	<OpeningComms.helpTexts>
		<li>To communicate, select a working colonist and right-click on the comms console.</li>
	</OpeningComms.helpTexts>
	
	<helpTexts>
		<li>You can change the PRIORITY of storage. Colonists will fill higher-priority storage first.</li>
	</helpTexts>
	
	<Wiki.helpTexts>
		<li>You can look up information in the WIKI.\n\nUse the link the bottom right of the screen.</li>
	</Wiki.helpTexts>
	
	<TradeGoodsMustBeNearBeacon.helpTexts>
      <li>You can only sell trade goods which are near an orbital trade beacon and not under a roof.</li>
    </TradeGoodsMustBeNearBeacon.helpTexts>
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	
	

</LanguageData>